so I am still very much in the confusion
of what this lesson is and all these
lessons are as they're unfolding and
happening because I there's stuff here
and I can tell it's around
confidentiality it's around leadership
it's around broadcast versus versus
distributed and it's around my own
anti-authority hierarchy stuff and how
much of that is real in what we need in
the world and how much is my own shadow
and and I need to get rid of it and
so the things have been dealing with
over the last few weeks the the
community piece which honestly is barely
a blip on the radar last time it was the
biggest event that year and this time
it's like yeah and it was a bigger event
really this time this time I was more
shocked not by the person who did it she
had done it before
but by like someone coming in not
leaving your doorway and insisting on
having the conversation you can't close
the door like that's just so ridiculous
still even a couple weeks later but I
don't feel like emotion or ground this
needs to go this way I'm just like yes
pretty can t interact I'll have to
figure that out
I'd love to figure out how to stay apart
in a tiny tiny community not physically
apart but you know like not talk to one
another not trigger one another and then
the Kyle sees thing which is both big
but it's also happened before in my life
I had a spiritual teacher who although
I'd never met him just like I've never
really met policies had a fall from
grace around a women and grouse nests of
spiritual like frosting the line that
wasn't illegal but what like just you
and this is also just like you and it's
I'm more do around the the lack of
integrity and authenticity and like my
story around who Kyle sees was and this
beautiful part that is like oh you're
not more evolved than me you truly are
evolving out loud and I'm evolving
faster and that's my own my own
story I don't think any one involves
fast I don't think anyone's more worthy
anyone else but like that I had him on a
pedestal without even quite realizing
and then when he knocked down it was
like oh no we are actually I'm more off
that dick I am dealing with my stuff
I am like this is who I am and as I
learn I like because I also have the
freedom to do that I don't have my money
tied up in this right I don't have I
could go viral for the wrong reason and
everyone could hate me but I still have
my family and friends I am safe enough
that I can do that and that's part of
the cost of leadership and of having a
movement and followers of any kind
whether their customers members clients
that there's a cost to them by you
falling from grace if you're the leader
and they're all following you but when
it's distributed that doesn't happen in
the same way and now I've been made an
admin auditor not actually quite clear
of the title for the game be Facebook
group and there's both like internal
feelings in me of like oh that's too
much and I don't know I have my and the
part of its true that the like executive
functioning of deciding what's
confidential and what's not and where am
I wearing and in Manhattan where am I
wearing
Jubilee hat where we read it together
tech hat and where am i wearing no hats
I just like what is what is that and
that's part of it and then like
confidentiality if being an it men and
my mission on this planet and especially
the guidance I'm getting right now is to
like share my journey authentically and
where there are barriers to that where
there are places I can't share that's a
problem for me and so that might be the
reason I have to leave the Amenti m--
but right now it feels like a good
tension it feels like this is my
learning to come up against like it's
like okay you have to figure out how to
follow a someone else's guidance right
like this group has its own guidance
then as you know has more some people
that are more leadership roles than
others and what I feel about that in
which I'm like you know is this this
person's Facebook group or is it game B
even if they're one of the people who
came up with game B and that brings up
other stuff with with brain tumor groups
that I could go into a whole other time
yeah just the like need for
confidentiality for this group and this
group has decided it so if I'm there I
have to follow that but at the same time
being able to share my journey
authentically and share
things that come up for me and so that
is a line I have to follow it is like
I'm gonna have to figure that out and I
might cross it sometimes and figure that
out and either when I cross it if I do
does that mean I have to leave I don't
think it'll be them I'm not gonna do
anything atrocious this is me I'll be
kicked out we can be completely and even
if I am game B still exists all around
and so that is just what I'm sitting
with the same for like leadership and
sovereignty and confidentiality and
following the stories the path thank you